David Ramm

Contact Information
Phone number: (512) 948-1282
Email Address: davidkramm@gmail.com

CAREER PROFILE

Experienced in Real Estate technology, start-up development, market research, and insights. Passionate and innovative thinker with experience in operational models and intricate planning. Relationally connected and well networked within the industry allowing for phenomenal growth. Strong problem solver with experience interpreting problems and finding solutions.

EDUCATION

LeTourneau University – Longview, Texas

May 2021

Major in Cybersecurity with a Minor in Business Administration

- Technological security solutions/ Business Solutions and Innovation; GPA 4.0
- New Venture Competition competitor
- Participated in event planning and organization through the YAC program

EXPERIENCE

RealQuik LLC- Austin, Texas

2017-Present

[The all in one solution to manage and facilitate Real Estate Transactions]

Chief Operating Officer/Co-founder

- Incorporated and executed an extensive business plan that has been recognized for excellence, create solutions, and market knowledge by the Baylor New Venture judges and investors.
- Developed creative technological solutions within the real estate industry.
- Experience with on-boarding employees through hundreds of interviews.
- Created and carried out an extensive market research campaign that reached many real estate agencies to pinpoint the target market.

WorldSnackPacks – Georgetown, Texas

2016-2017

Chief Executive Officer

[Get foreign snacks delivered right to your doorstep]

- Created an extensive plan for distribution of foreign snacks on a national level.
- Developed innovative solutions for packaging supplies through structure and dimension.
- Conducted research for supplies and created an extensive list of useful products based on size and dimension.

Ribbon Road Farm— Sherman, New York

2012-2013

Employee

[Organic Garlic]

- Managed the appropriate placement of produce based on relative size and density.
- Distributed the produce according to farm regulations.
- Created a pump system to irrigate the produce as needed.

ADDITIONAL

- Real Estate knowledge and insight obtained through the 180-hour Texas real estate pre-licensing course
- Has been recognized for top academic achievement in The Sun Newspaper
- 2A Intramural activities and team building
- LeTourneau Dean's List
- Placed in the top 16th percentile for the Baylor New Venture competition